Everyone pays in the end.
Absolution is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Hans Petter Moland.
An aging ex-boxer gangster working as muscle for a Boston
crime boss receives an upsetting diagnosis.
Despite a faltering memory, he attempts to rectify the sins of his
past and reconnect with his estranged children.
He is determined to leave a positive legacy for his grandson, but the criminal
underworld isn’t done with him and won’t loosen their grip willingly.
Thug, played by Liam Neeson.
Charlie Conner, played by Ron Perlman.
Woman, played by Yolonda Ross.
Daisy, played by Frankie Shaw.
Kyle Conner, played by Daniel Diemer.
Diego Machado, played by Jimmy Gonzáles.
Absolution is a 2024 American action thriller film directed by Hans Petter Moland, written
by Tony Gayton, and starring Liam Neeson as a brooding, aging gangster.
Absolution was theatrically released on November 1, 2024 by Samuel
Goldwyn Films, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.